WEI TING CHANG

(626)-224-7367 | chang.weit@husky.neu.edu

PROFILE

A certified pharmacist with 2 years of research experience and educational background across Cell Biology, Microbiology, Pharmaceutical Sciences and Immunology. Experienced in mammalian cell culture, immunoassay development (Western blot/ELISA), monoclonal antibody purification, and in vivo/ in vitro image improvement study. Seeking for Research Associate position where I can contribute my strong analytical skills and experience.

SKILLS

- Cell Culture/FACS Flow Cytometry Western blot/ELISA RT-PCR Transfection Fluorescent microscopy
- HPLC Immunohistochemistry Affinity and Size- Exclusion Chromatography Cytotoxicity

- Software Package used for Statistical Analysis (SPSS)
- Gen 5TM Data Analysis MS Office

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Research Assistant at Dr. Ban An Khaw's lab, Northeastern University

Jan. 2014 - Present

- "Signal Amplification by pretargeting with Bispecific Antibody"
 - Purified antimyosin monoclonal / bispecific antibody by affinity and size-exclusion chromatography
 - Performed ELISA, Western blot and HPLC for characterization of antimyosin monoclonal / bispecific antibody
 - Conducted bioconjugation of RITC and DTPA to poly-L-lysine for immunochemistry image improvement
 - Produced functional affibody by using recombinant plasmid in E.coli cells and His-tagged antigen columns
- "Quantitation of Myosin Heavy Chain Isoform for Assessment of the Severity of Hypertrophic Cardiomyopathy"
 - Performed *in vivo* studies (extracted myosin from the cardiac and skeletal muscles of mice)
 - Identified antimyosin murine hybridoma cell clones by limiting dilution analysis
 - Present poster "Changes in Isoforms of Cardiac Myosin in Hypertrophic Rat model of anemia" at International Society for Pharmaceutical Engineering 2015

Graduate School of Biochemistry Laboratory, Taipei Medical University

Sep.2009 - July 2010

- Familiarized with cell culture aseptic techniques (maintained GBM-8401 cell line)
- Performed FACS flow cytometry to study apoptotic/autophagic GBM-8401 cell death after LiCl treatment

EDUCATION

Northeastern University, Boston, MA

Master of Pharmaceutical Sciences (Pharmaceutics and Drug Delivery Systems)

Expected: Aug. 2015 Current GPA: 3.86/4.00

Taipei Medical University, Taipei, Taiwan

June 2012

Bachelor of Science, Pharmacy

GPA: 3 81/4 00

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teaching Assistant at Dr. Kari Furtek, Northeastern University

Sep. 2014 - Dec. 2014

Managed Pharm.D. students in Comprehensive Disease Management course

Pharmacist at Chius Eye Clinic, Taipei, Taiwan

Jan. 2013 - July 2013

• Consulted with physicians and dispensed prescription drugs and provided drug safety information to patients

Pharmacist License (License number: 038099), Taipei, Taiwan CERTIFICATION

Oct. 2012

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

• The Chair of Memberships in American Association of Pharmaceutical Scientists (NEU-student Chapter)

2015